(slow rock music)
♪ Now that she's back in the atmosphere ♪
♪ With drops of Jupiter in her hair ♪
♪ She acts like summer
and walks like rain ♪
♪ Reminds me that there's
a time to change, hey ♪
♪ Since the return of
her stay on the moon ♪
♪ She listens like spring and
she talks like June, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, yeah ♪
♪ But tell me, did you
sail across the sun ♪
♪ Did you make it to the Milky Way ♪
♪ To see the lights all faded ♪
♪ And that Heaven is overrated ♪
♪ And tell me, did you
fall for a shooting star ♪
♪ One without a permanent
scar, and did you miss me ♪
♪ While you were looking
for yourself out there ♪
♪ Now that she's back
from that soul vacation ♪
♪ Tracing her way through
the constellation, hey, mmm ♪
♪ She checks out Mozart
while she does Tae-Bo ♪
♪ Reminds me that there's
a room to grow, hey, yeah ♪
♪ Now that she's back in the atmosphere ♪
♪ I'm afraid that she
might think of me as ♪
♪ Plain ol' Jane told
a story about a man ♪
♪ Who was too afraid to
fly, so he never did land ♪
♪ But tell me, did the wind
sweep you off your feet ♪
♪ Did you finally get the chance ♪
♪ To dance along the light of day ♪
♪ And head back to the Milky Way ♪
♪ And tell me, did Venus blow your mind ♪
♪ Was it everything you wanted
to find, and did you miss me ♪
♪ While you were looking
for yourself out there ♪
♪ Can you imagine no love,
pride, deep-fried chicken ♪
♪ Your best friend always
sticking up for you ♪
♪ Even when I know you're wrong ♪
♪ Can you imagine no first
dance, freeze-dried romance ♪
♪ Five hour phone conversation ♪
♪ The best soy latte that
you ever had, and me ♪
♪ But tell me, did the wind
sweep you off your feet ♪
♪ Did you finally get the chance ♪
♪ To dance along the light of day ♪
♪ And head back toward the Milky Way ♪
♪ And tell me, did you
sail across the sun ♪
♪ Did you make it to the Milky Way ♪
♪ To see the lights all faded ♪
♪ And that Heaven is overrated ♪
♪ And tell me, did you
fall for a shooting star ♪
♪ One without a permanent
scar, and then you miss me ♪
♪ While you were looking for yourself ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na, na, na ♪
♪ And did you finally get the chance ♪
♪ To dance along the light of day ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na, na, na ♪
♪ And did you fall for a shooting star ♪
♪ Fall for a shooting star ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na, na, na ♪
♪ And are you lonely looking
for yourself out there ♪